{
    "id": "3afc26fcb5064b94867eac27f230c8f2",
    "title": "Conjunctions Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "John smokes .................................. his brother doesnâ€™t.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "but",
                "and",
                "so"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "09fca31de58b4be296d3547e265b49c0"
        },
        {
            "question": "Neither Alice ......................................... Mary has come.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "nor"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "39902093bd604a50b6d19cd2663ca938"
        },
        {
            "question": "She speaks English .................................... Spanish.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as well as",
                "and",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "790a8e40b5bf4d2bbe625fe26209c925"
        },
        {
            "question": "I like him ...................................... he is very sincere.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "because",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "07408b4f2e8548d199654583f68740f1"
        },
        {
            "question": "..................................... he worked hard, he did not win.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Though",
                "As if",
                "As though"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "d7c44416180148568cc442e659ab4d80"
        },
        {
            "question": "She is ill ................................ she is cheerful.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "but",
                "as well as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "5f168f78590b4e4ba065083b8350b249"
        },
        {
            "question": "...................................... it was raining we decided to go out.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "Despite",
                "Though",
                "However"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "d7ca4bebf4d446a1904bdd40aee8a5d1"
        },
        {
            "question": "The piper played ...................................... the children danced.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "or",
                "and",
                "but"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "81f2b90224214ebabe4c1797fd26aed2"
        },
        {
            "question": "James works hard ....................................... his brother is lazy.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "as",
                "as long as",
                "whereas"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "36589c37b1744323a223c1b1fa943489"
        },
        {
            "question": "I went to the shop ..................................... bought some vegetables.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "and",
                "so",
                "hence"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "48645fedd10e4950894427d8fc85771e"
        },
        {
            "question": "You must start at once ................................. you will be late.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "whereas",
                "otherwise",
                "as long as"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "fd9c5a406221470197e865dee33a43a5"
        },
        {
            "question": "He must be tired ..................................... he has been working since morning.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "so",
                "hence",
                "because"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "0617c61e2f9047638fa23699a6df2661"
        }
    ]
}